{
    "Harry Potter": [
        {
            "question": "What Hogwarts house does Harry Potter Belong to?",
            "answer": "Gryffindor",
            "options":[
                "Slytherin", 
                "Hufflepuff", 
                "Ravenclaw",
                "Gryffindor"
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "How are students sorted into their houses?",
            "answer": "Sorting Hat",
            "options": [
                "Sorting Hat",
                "Sorting Test", 
                "Sorting Ceremony", 
                "Sorting Wand"
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "What house is Draco Malfoy sorted into?",
            "answer": "Slytherin",
            "options": [
                "RavenClaw", 
                "Hufflepuff",
                "Gryffindor",
                "Slytherin"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question": "What wandcore does Harry Potters wand have?",
            "answer": "Pheonix Feather",
            "options": [
                "Unicorn Hair",
                "Dragon Heart String",
                "Pheonix Feather",
                "Troll Hair"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question": "In the goblet of fire what did Harry Potter have to rescue from the dragons nest?",
            "answer": "A Golden Egg",
            "options": [
                "A Broom",
                "A Golden Egg",
                "A Golden Snitch",
                "A Map"
            ]
        }
    ],

    "One Piece": [
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Monkey D Luffys Devil Fruit ?",
            "answer": "Gomu Gomu No Mi",
            "options":[
                " Magu Magu No Mi",
                "Goro Goro No Mi",
                "Gomu Gomu No Mi",
                "Ope Ope No Mi"
                ]
        },


        {
           " Question": "How many swords does Roronoa Zoro use when fighting ?", 
            "answer": "3",
            "options": [
                "3",
                "1",
                "9",
                "2"
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "What kind of animal is Tony Chopper ?",
            "answer":"Reindeer",

            "options": [
                "Otter",
                "Lion",
                "Reindeer",
                "Rabbit"
                ]
        }, 

        {
            "question": "What is the name of Monkey D Luffy's first ship?",
            "answer": "Going Merry ",
            "options": [
                "Thousand Sunny",
                "Going Merry ",
                "Red Force",
                "The Flying Dutchman"
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "What is painted on Moneky D Luffy's Jolly Roger ?",
            "answer": "A Skull and Bones wearing a straw hat",
            "options": [
                "A Skull and Bones surronded by sweets", 
                "A Skull and Bones with three scars",
                "A Skull and Bones wearing a top hat",
                "A Skull and Bones wearing a straw hat"
            ]
        } 
    ],

    "PlayStation": [
            {
                "question": "What is the name of the studio that produced The Last Of Us?",
                "answer": "Naughty Dog",
                "options": [
                    "Naughty Dog",
                    "343 Studios",
                    "Blizzard",
                    "Sucker Punch"
                ]
            }, 

            {
                "question": "What Marvel franchise is Insomniac famouse for developing?",
                "answer": "Spiderman",
                "options":[
                    "Wolverine",
                    "The Hulk",
                    "Batman",
                    "Spiderman"
                ] 
            },
            
           {
                "question": "What colour is the PlayStation 5?",
                "answer": "White and Black",
                "options": [
                    "White and Black",
                    "Black and Blue",
                    "Pink and Red",
                    "Blue and White"
                ]
            },

            {
                "question": "What is the name of the main character in God of war?",
                "answer": "Kratos",
                "options": [
                    "Zeus", 
                    "Aries", 
                    "Jeff",
                    "Kratos"
                ] 
            },

            {
                "question": "How many main line Uncharted games have been released ?",
                "answer": "5",
                "options":[
                    "4",
                    "2",
                    "5",
                    "7"
                ]
            } 
        ],

    "Sports" :[
        {
            "question": "Which country has won the most soccer World Cups?",
            "answer": "Brazil",
            "options": [
                "Germany",
                "Brazil",
                "France",
                "South Africa"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question": "In which year did China host the Olympics?",
            "answer": "2008",
            "options": [
                "2008",
                "2004",
                "2012",
                "2000"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question": "How many rugby World Cups has South Africa won?",
            "answer": "3",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "4",
                "3"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question":"What is the 100m sprint record?",
            "answer": "9.58s",
            "options": [
                "9.78s",
                "9.85s", 
                "9.52s",
                "9.58s"
            ]
        },    

        {
            "question":"Who has the most F1 Driver's Championships?",
            "answer": "Lewis Hamilton",
            "options": [
                "Lewis Hamilton",
                "Fernando Alonso",
                "Sebastian Vettel",
                "NikiLaude"
            ]
        } 
    ],

    "Geography" :[
        {
            "question":"What is the largest continent in size?",
            "answer": "Asia",
            "options": [
                "Africa",
                "Europe",
                "North America",
                "Asia"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question":"Which is the smallest country in size?",
            "answer": "Vatican City",
            "options": [
                "Naura",
                "Tonga",
                "Vatican City",
                "Samoa"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question":"In which country is the tallest mountain?",
            "answer": "Nepal",
            "options": [
                "Nepal",
                "Switzerland",
                "Greenland",
                "Slovakia"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question":"Which is the largest ocean?",
            "answer": "Pacific Ocean",
            "options": [
                "Atlantic Ocean",
                "Indian Ocean",
                "Arctic Ocean",
                "Pacific Ocean"
            ] 
        },

        {
            "question":"What is the size of the Sahara desert?",
            "answer": "9 200 000 km2",
            "options": [
                "10 000 000 km2", 
                "9 500 000 km2 ", 
                "9 000 000 km2",
                "9 200 000 km2"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question":"What is the capital of Italy?",
            "answer": "Rome",
            "options": [
                "Florence", 
                "Venice", 
                "Naples",
                "Rome"
            ]
        } 
    ],

    "Science" : [
        {
            "question": "What does a 'light year' measure?",
            "answer": "Distance",
            "options": [
                "Distance",
                "Sound", 
                "Time",
                "Speed"
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "Photosynthesis is a process created by?",
            "answer": "Plants",
            "options": [
                "Animals", 
                "Food", 
                "Cameras",
                "Plants"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question": "How many bones are in the human body?",
            "answer": "206",
            "options": [
                "106", 
                "156", 
                "256",
                "206"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question": "How much of the Earth's surface is covered in water?",
            "answer": "70%",
            "options": [
                "20%",
                "70%",
                "40%",
                "50%"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "question": "In which food will you find the most Vitamin C?",
            "answer": "Vitamin C",
            "options": [
                "Vitamin C",
                "Meat",
                "Fish",
                "Cereal"
            ]
        }
    ], 
    "Math":[
        {
            "question": "121 Divided by 11 is",
            "answer": "11",
            "options": [
                "11",
                "10",
                "19",
                "18"
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "Solve 3 + 6 ร ( 5 + 4) รท 3 - 7",
            "answer": "14",
            "options": [
                "11",
                "16",
                "14",
                "15"
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "Solve 23 + 3 รท 3",
            "answer": "24",
            "options": [
                "24",
                "25",
                "26",
                "27"
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "Add the Decimals 5.23 + 8.79",
            "answer": "14.02",
            "options": [
                "14.19",
                "14.11",
                "14.02",
                "14.29"
            ]
        },
        
        {
            "question": "The Product of 131 x 0 x 300 x 4",
            "answer": "0",
            "options": [
                "11",
                "0",
                "46",
                "45"
            ]
        }
    ]

}
